

CONTACT

703-402-0154

✓ nathanielrconrad@gmail.com

Q Washington, D.C.



SKILLS

- Web Design
- Wireframe Creation (Figma)
- Front End Coding (CSS, JS)
- Problem-Solving (Data Structures & Algorithms)
- Computer Literacy (Windows, Mac)
- Project Management Tools (Jira)
- Strong Communication
- Mandarin Chinese

EDUCATION

BROWN UNIVERSITY

BA East Asian Studies 2019

Degree with Honors, Magna Cum Laude, Phi Beta Kappa

YUNNAN NORMAL UNIVERSITY, BEIJING NORMAL UNIVERSITY

Chinese Culture & Philosophy

2015-2017

NATE CONRAD

WEB DEVELOPER

PROFILE

I am a self-driven, self-taught developer of web applications to serve practical business needs. My background is in program direction, investment research, and renewable energy sales, so I also bring effective communication and a cooperative, upbeat spirit to any team I join.

EXPERIENCE

MARKETER, DEVELOPER

Capitalist Times

2017 - Present

- Designed and developed sales lander webpage and widgets in HTML/CSS/JS
- Edited Renewable Energy Investment publication which earned 2k+ sales
- Researched global LNG trends, esp. in China

OPERATIONS DIRECTOR, RULE OF LAW DIRECTOR

US-Asia Institute 2018-Present

- Organized legal education curriculum, moderated track 2 US-China diplomatic meetings
- Designed US Congressional briefings, educational materials for Chinese government delegations
- Hired, managed 15+ interns

FIELD SALES REPRESENTATIVE

Clean Choice Energy

06/2021 - 12/2021

- Persuaded 140+ DC and MD households to purchase more expensive renewable energy
- Earned CCE salesperson of the month 9/21 & 10/21
- Trained new hires